pale powdery
\hpale powdery
lichen
Which has dispersed itself with
happy
irregularity
So as to bring the red brick
into terms of friendly
companionship with a limestone
ornaments surrounding the three
gables the
windows and the doorplace
But the windows are patched
with wooden panes, and the door
I think is like the gate
It is never opened
For it is a solid, heavy,
handsome door
And must once have been in the
habit of shutting with a
sonorous bang
Pind the livered lackey who had
just seen his master and
mistress off the
grounds in a carriage and pair
A large open fireplace with
rusty dogs in it
Bear boarded floor
The far end fleeces of wolves
stacked up
In the middle of the floor,
some empty corn bags
And what through the left hand
window
Several
clotheshorses, a pillion, a
spinning wheel
In an old box wide open and
stuffed full of coloured rags
At the edge of this box, there
lies a great wooden doll
Which so far as mutilation is
concerned
There‘s a strong resemblance to
the finest Greek sculpture, and
especially in the total loss of
its nose
The history of the house is
plain now
But there is always a stronger
sense of life when the sun is
brilliant after rain
And now he is pouring down his
beams and making
sparkles among the wet straw
And lighting up every patch of
vivid green moss on the red
tiles of the cowshed
And turning even the muddy
water that is hurrying along
the channel to the drain
A mirror
Yellow billed
ducks who were seizing the
opportunity of getting a drink
As much body in it as possible
For the great barn doors are
thrown wide open and men are
busy there mending the
harness under the
superintendence of Mister
Gobe, the Whida, otherwise
saddler
Entertains them with the latest
Tredleston gossip
Hetty Sir often took the
opportunity when her aunt‘s
back was turned
Looking at the pleasing
reflection of
herself in those polished
services For the oak table was
using turned up like a screen
and was more for ornament than
for use
And she could see
herself sometimes in the great
round pewter dishes that were
ranged on the shelves above the
long deal dinner table
In the hobs of the great, which
always shone like Jasper
Do not suppose, however, that
Mrs.
Poyser was elderly or shrewish
in her appearance
She was a good looking woman
Not more than eight and thirty
Fair
complexion and sandy hair
Well shaping light footed